const quizDataFromFile = [
  {
    "question": "antworten",
    "correct": "to answer",
    "choices": [
      "to look / search for",
      "at the bottom",
      "to invite / treat",
      "to answer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(sich) anziehen",
    "correct": "to get dressed",
    "choices": [
      "to eat",
      "to come",
      "to thank",
      "to get dressed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "arbeiten",
    "correct": "to work",
    "choices": [
      "to work",
      "to give",
      "to look forward",
      "to sign"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "aufhören",
    "correct": "to end",
    "choices": [
      "together",
      "to drink",
      "to end",
      "to like"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "aufstehen",
    "correct": "to get up",
    "choices": [
      "to get up",
      "would like to",
      "to stay overnight",
      "to buy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ausfüllen",
    "correct": "to fill out",
    "choices": [
      "to eat",
      "to get on (board)",
      "to fill out",
      "to be"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ausmachen",
    "correct": "to switch off",
    "choices": [
      "to be able to",
      "to visit",
      "to get on (board)",
      "to switch off"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "aussehen",
    "correct": "to look",
    "choices": [
      "to look",
      "would like to",
      "to shine",
      "…"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "aussteigen",
    "correct": "to alight",
    "choices": [
      "to ask",
      "to alight",
      "against",
      "allow"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ausziehen",
    "correct": "to take off",
    "choices": [
      "to be",
      "to meet",
      "to take off",
      "to walk/run"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "sich ausziehen",
    "correct": "to get undressed",
    "choices": [
      "to (have a) barbecue",
      "to stay",
      "to make",
      "to get undressed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "baden",
    "correct": "to bathe",
    "choices": [
      "to learn",
      "to bathe",
      "to invite / treat",
      "to wash"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "bedeuten",
    "correct": "to mean",
    "choices": [
      "his",
      "to work",
      "to mean",
      "to answer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "beginnen",
    "correct": "to begin",
    "choices": [
      "to understand",
      "to (have a) barbecue",
      "to speak",
      "to begin"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "bekommen",
    "correct": "to receive/to have/to get",
    "choices": [
      "to mean",
      "to stay",
      "to receive/to have/to get",
      "to take with"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "benutzen",
    "correct": "to use",
    "choices": [
      "to see",
      "to use",
      "to take off",
      "to cook"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "besichtigen",
    "correct": "to visit",
    "choices": [
      "to telephone",
      "to believe",
      "to find",
      "to visit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "bestellen",
    "correct": "to order",
    "choices": [
      "to be",
      "to wash",
      "to hear",
      "to order"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "besuchen",
    "correct": "to visit",
    "choices": [
      "to live",
      "against",
      "to walk/run",
      "to visit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "bezahlen",
    "correct": "to pay",
    "choices": [
      "to marry",
      "to pay",
      "to cook",
      "to like"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "bisschen",
    "correct": "(a) little",
    "choices": [
      "to dance",
      "to get dressed",
      "to say / tell",
      "(a) little"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "bitten",
    "correct": "to ask",
    "choices": [
      "to ask",
      "to write",
      "to become",
      "to taste"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "bleiben",
    "correct": "to stay",
    "choices": [
      "to dance",
      "to come with",
      "to stay",
      "to be missing"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "brauchen",
    "correct": "to need",
    "choices": [
      "to rent out",
      "to fill out",
      "to need",
      "to be missing"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "bringen",
    "correct": "to bring/to take",
    "choices": [
      "to print",
      "to bring/to take",
      "to put",
      "to drink"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "buchstabieren",
    "correct": "to spell",
    "choices": [
      "between",
      "to wait",
      "to spell",
      "to be missing"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "daneben",
    "correct": "next to it",
    "choices": [
      "to depart (by air)",
      "to go",
      "to wash",
      "next to it"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "danken",
    "correct": "to thank",
    "choices": [
      "to play",
      "to congratulate",
      "to thank",
      "to get undressed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "draußen",
    "correct": "outside",
    "choices": [
      "outside",
      "between",
      "to sleep",
      "to fly"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "drucken",
    "correct": "to print",
    "choices": [
      "to print",
      "to live",
      "to walk/run",
      "to open"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "drücken",
    "correct": "to press",
    "choices": [
      "to press",
      "to sit",
      "seven",
      "to take with"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "dürfen",
    "correct": "to be allowed",
    "choices": [
      "to dance",
      "to fly",
      "to love",
      "to be allowed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(sich) duschen",
    "correct": "to shower",
    "choices": [
      "one million",
      "to take",
      "to live",
      "to shower"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "einkaufen",
    "correct": "to go shopping",
    "choices": [
      "to be",
      "to go shopping",
      "one million",
      "should"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "einladen",
    "correct": "to invite / treat",
    "choices": [
      "to come with",
      "to take",
      "to invite / treat",
      "to be (located)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "einsteigen",
    "correct": "to get on (board)",
    "choices": [
      "to see",
      "to recommend",
      "to get on (board)",
      "to get to know"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "empfehlen",
    "correct": "to recommend",
    "choices": [
      "to be",
      "to live",
      "to recommend",
      "to (have a) barbecue"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "enden",
    "correct": "to end",
    "choices": [
      "to get on (board)",
      "to play",
      "to telephone",
      "to end"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "entschuldigen",
    "correct": "to excuse",
    "choices": [
      "to excuse",
      "together",
      "to love",
      "to shine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "erklären",
    "correct": "to explain",
    "choices": [
      "tomorrow",
      "to explain",
      "to make",
      "to pay"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "erlauben",
    "correct": "allow",
    "choices": [
      "died",
      "allow",
      "to get dressed",
      "to visit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "erzählen",
    "correct": "to tell",
    "choices": [
      "to tell",
      "outside",
      "to order",
      "to swim"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "essen",
    "correct": "to eat",
    "choices": [
      "to eat",
      "to stop",
      "to end",
      "…"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "fahren",
    "correct": "to travel",
    "choices": [
      "to taste",
      "to get up",
      "to depart (by air)",
      "to travel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "fehlen",
    "correct": "to be absent/to be missing",
    "choices": [
      "to tell",
      "to sleep",
      "to be absent/to be missing",
      "to order"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "fernsehen",
    "correct": "to watch TV",
    "choices": [
      "to watch TV",
      "to listen",
      "to end",
      "to transfer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "finden",
    "correct": "to find",
    "choices": [
      "to receive",
      "to end",
      "to find",
      "against"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "fliegen",
    "correct": "to fly",
    "choices": [
      "to ask",
      "to use",
      "to take off",
      "to fly"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "abfliegen",
    "correct": "to depart (by air)",
    "choices": [
      "to depart (by air)",
      "to go",
      "to order",
      "should"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "fragen",
    "correct": "to ask",
    "choices": [
      "to ask",
      "to come",
      "to be missing",
      "to answer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(sich) freuen",
    "correct": "to look forward",
    "choices": [
      "to have",
      "to read",
      "to look forward",
      "to move (residence)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "frühstücken",
    "correct": "to have breakfast",
    "choices": [
      "together",
      "to end",
      "allow",
      "to have breakfast"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "geben",
    "correct": "to give",
    "choices": [
      "to look / search for",
      "to rain",
      "to give",
      "to repeat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "geboren",
    "correct": "born",
    "choices": [
      "born",
      "at the bottom",
      "to be allowed",
      "to explain"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "gefallen",
    "correct": "to like",
    "choices": [
      "to understand",
      "to be missing",
      "to order",
      "to like"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "gegen",
    "correct": "against",
    "choices": [
      "to meet",
      "against",
      "to hear",
      "to believe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "gehen",
    "correct": "to work/function/to go/to be okay",
    "choices": [
      "to watch TV",
      "to work/function/to go/to be okay",
      "to be",
      "…"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "gehören",
    "correct": "to belong",
    "choices": [
      "to belong",
      "to stay overnight",
      "to buy",
      "to sign"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "gestorben",
    "correct": "died",
    "choices": [
      "to switch off",
      "to introduce",
      "died",
      "to have to"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "gewinnen",
    "correct": "to win",
    "choices": [
      "to win",
      "to repeat",
      "to have to",
      "to sell"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "glauben",
    "correct": "to believe/to think",
    "choices": [
      "to answer",
      "against",
      "to be allowed",
      "to believe/to think"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "gratulieren",
    "correct": "to congratulate",
    "choices": [
      "to dance",
      "to work",
      "to ask",
      "to congratulate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "grillen",
    "correct": "to (have a) barbecue",
    "choices": [
      "to excuse",
      "to depart (by air)",
      "to win",
      "to (have a) barbecue"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "haben",
    "correct": "to have",
    "choices": [
      "to stop",
      "to open",
      "to know",
      "to have"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "halten",
    "correct": "to stop",
    "choices": [
      "to stop",
      "to marry",
      "to go",
      "to ask"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "heiraten",
    "correct": "to marry",
    "choices": [
      "to marry",
      "to stay overnight",
      "to laugh",
      "to switch off"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "heißen",
    "correct": "to be called",
    "choices": [
      "to live",
      "between",
      "to be called",
      "to want"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "helfen",
    "correct": "to help",
    "choices": [
      "to live",
      "to help",
      "to get undressed",
      "to open"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "hinten",
    "correct": "at/in the back",
    "choices": [
      "at/in the back",
      "to be allowed",
      "to hear",
      "one million"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "holen",
    "correct": "to fetch",
    "choices": [
      "to come",
      "to earn",
      "to order",
      "to fetch"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "hören",
    "correct": "to listen/to hear",
    "choices": [
      "to rent",
      "to listen/to hear",
      "against",
      "to be absent"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "kaufen",
    "correct": "to buy",
    "choices": [
      "to write",
      "to bring with one / to get (sth. for sb.)",
      "to invite / treat",
      "to buy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "kennen",
    "correct": "to know",
    "choices": [
      "to know",
      "to get",
      "to help",
      "to press"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "kennenlernen",
    "correct": "to get to know",
    "choices": [
      "upstairs",
      "to end",
      "to travel",
      "to get to know"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "kochen",
    "correct": "to cook",
    "choices": [
      "to belong",
      "to drink",
      "to be allowed",
      "to cook"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "kommen",
    "correct": "to come",
    "choices": [
      "to win",
      "to come",
      "to bring",
      "to speak"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "können",
    "correct": "to be able to",
    "choices": [
      "to be able to",
      "to join in",
      "to work/function",
      "to open"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "kosten",
    "correct": "to cost",
    "choices": [
      "to listen",
      "to cost",
      "to press",
      "to sleep"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "kriegen",
    "correct": "to get",
    "choices": [
      "to get",
      "between",
      "to order",
      "to transfer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "lachen",
    "correct": "to laugh",
    "choices": [
      "to get on (board)",
      "to get",
      "to telephone",
      "to laugh"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "laufen",
    "correct": "to walk/run",
    "choices": [
      "at/in the back",
      "to get",
      "to walk/run",
      "to shower"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "leben",
    "correct": "to live",
    "choices": [
      "to understand",
      "to live",
      "to come",
      "to cost"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "legen",
    "correct": "to put",
    "choices": [
      "one million",
      "to come",
      "to put",
      "to be allowed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "lernen",
    "correct": "to learn",
    "choices": [
      "to learn",
      "to live",
      "to pay",
      "to recommend"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "lesen",
    "correct": "to read",
    "choices": [
      "to switch off",
      "happy",
      "to get dressed",
      "to read"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "lieben",
    "correct": "to love",
    "choices": [
      "to come",
      "to love",
      "to fetch",
      "should"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "liegen",
    "correct": "to lie / be located",
    "choices": [
      "to lie / be located",
      "to want",
      "to travel",
      "to read"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "machen",
    "correct": "to do/to make/to come to",
    "choices": [
      "to do/to make/to come to",
      "to get",
      "to pay",
      "to find"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "mieten",
    "correct": "to rent",
    "choices": [
      "to rent",
      "to get up",
      "to drink",
      "to get"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "mitbringen",
    "correct": "to bring with one / to get (sth. for sb.)",
    "choices": [
      "to come",
      "to bring with one / to get (sth. for sb.)",
      "to walk/run",
      "to take"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "mitkommen",
    "correct": "to come with",
    "choices": [
      "to come with",
      "to sign",
      "to mean",
      "to buy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "mitmachen",
    "correct": "to join in",
    "choices": [
      "to join in",
      "to bathe",
      "to sleep",
      "to find"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "mitnehmen",
    "correct": "to take with",
    "choices": [
      "to get",
      "to take off",
      "to like",
      "to take with"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "möchten",
    "correct": "would like to",
    "choices": [
      "to work/function",
      "would like to",
      "to travel",
      "to have (food/drink)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "mögen",
    "correct": "to like",
    "choices": [
      "to join in",
      "to stay",
      "to cost",
      "to like"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "morgen",
    "correct": "tomorrow",
    "choices": [
      "tomorrow",
      "to think",
      "to shower",
      "to spell"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "müssen",
    "correct": "to have to",
    "choices": [
      "to sit",
      "to get undressed",
      "to have to",
      "to transfer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "nehmen",
    "correct": "to have (food/drink)/to take",
    "choices": [
      "to stay",
      "to invite / treat",
      "to have (food/drink)/to take",
      "to want"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "oben",
    "correct": "upstairs",
    "choices": [
      "upstairs",
      "to explain",
      "to go",
      "to open"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "öffnen",
    "correct": "to open",
    "choices": [
      "to be (written)",
      "to explain",
      "to find",
      "to open"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Rad fahren",
    "correct": "to cycle",
    "choices": [
      "to close",
      "outside",
      "to live",
      "to cycle"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "rauchen",
    "correct": "to smoke",
    "choices": [
      "to smoke",
      "to belong",
      "to bathe",
      "to hear"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "regnen",
    "correct": "to rain",
    "choices": [
      "to know",
      "to rain",
      "to buy",
      "to visit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "reisen",
    "correct": "to travel",
    "choices": [
      "to tell",
      "to help",
      "his",
      "to travel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "reparieren",
    "correct": "to repair",
    "choices": [
      "to play",
      "to get",
      "to be allowed",
      "to repair"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "riechen",
    "correct": "to smell",
    "choices": [
      "to visit",
      "to depart (by air)",
      "to smell",
      "to take with"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "sagen",
    "correct": "to say / tell",
    "choices": [
      "into",
      "to say / tell",
      "to sit",
      "to be okay"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "scheinen",
    "correct": "to shine",
    "choices": [
      "to print",
      "to wash",
      "to shine",
      "to begin"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "schicken",
    "correct": "to send",
    "choices": [
      "to cycle",
      "to send",
      "to come with",
      "to write"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "schlafen",
    "correct": "to sleep",
    "choices": [
      "to sleep",
      "to laugh",
      "to wait",
      "to shine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "schließen",
    "correct": "to close",
    "choices": [
      "to close",
      "to belong",
      "to give",
      "to speak"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "geschlossen",
    "correct": "closed",
    "choices": [
      "to bathe",
      "between",
      "to be absent",
      "closed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "schmecken",
    "correct": "to taste",
    "choices": [
      "to taste",
      "to take",
      "to learn",
      "to shine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "schreiben",
    "correct": "to write",
    "choices": [
      "to write",
      "born",
      "to take",
      "to look / search for"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "schwimmen",
    "correct": "to swim",
    "choices": [
      "to spell",
      "to help",
      "between",
      "to swim"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "sehen",
    "correct": "to see",
    "choices": [
      "to see",
      "to live",
      "to marry",
      "to get dressed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "sein (er)",
    "correct": "his",
    "choices": [
      "to be (written)",
      "to drink",
      "his",
      "to believe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "sein",
    "correct": "to be",
    "choices": [
      "to be",
      "to put",
      "died",
      "to be called"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "sitzen",
    "correct": "to sit",
    "choices": [
      "to sit",
      "to travel",
      "to spell",
      "to have"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "sollen",
    "correct": "should",
    "choices": [
      "against",
      "to end",
      "to find",
      "should"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "spielen",
    "correct": "to play",
    "choices": [
      "to play",
      "to stay overnight",
      "to travel",
      "one billion"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "sprechen",
    "correct": "to speak",
    "choices": [
      "to be",
      "to depart (by air)",
      "to go",
      "to speak"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "stehen",
    "correct": "to be (written)/to be (located)",
    "choices": [
      "to listen",
      "to lie",
      "to be (written)to be (located)",
      "to (have a) barbecue"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "stellen",
    "correct": "to put",
    "choices": [
      "to stay",
      "to put",
      "to be allowed",
      "to walk/run"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "studieren",
    "correct": "to study",
    "choices": [
      "to stay",
      "to study",
      "between",
      "would like to"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "suchen",
    "correct": "to look / search for",
    "choices": [
      "to smoke",
      "to look / search for",
      "to pay",
      "to excuse"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "tanzen",
    "correct": "to dance",
    "choices": [
      "to dance",
      "to do",
      "to get on (board)",
      "to spell"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "telefonieren",
    "correct": "to telephone",
    "choices": [
      "to dance",
      "to telephone",
      "to order",
      "to begin"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(sich) treffen",
    "correct": "to meet",
    "choices": [
      "to do",
      "to meet",
      "to sleep",
      "to be okay"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "trinken",
    "correct": "to drink",
    "choices": [
      "to smoke",
      "to drink",
      "to like",
      "should"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "übernachten",
    "correct": "to stay overnight",
    "choices": [
      "outside",
      "to live",
      "to stay overnight",
      "to sign"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "überweisen",
    "correct": "to transfer",
    "choices": [
      "outside",
      "between",
      "to become",
      "to transfer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "umziehen",
    "correct": "to move (residence)",
    "choices": [
      "to have (food/drink)",
      "seven",
      "to order",
      "to move (residence)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "unten",
    "correct": "at the bottom",
    "choices": [
      "to ask",
      "at the bottom",
      "to invite / treat",
      "to read"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "unterschreiben",
    "correct": "to sign",
    "choices": [
      "to buy",
      "to look forward",
      "to have (food/drink)",
      "to sign"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "verboten",
    "correct": "forbidden",
    "choices": [
      "to work/function",
      "forbidden",
      "to earn",
      "together"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "verdienen",
    "correct": "to earn",
    "choices": [
      "to learn",
      "to live",
      "to earn",
      "to stay overnight"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "verkaufen",
    "correct": "to sell",
    "choices": [
      "born",
      "to read",
      "to spell",
      "to sell"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "vermieten",
    "correct": "to rent out",
    "choices": [
      "to (have a) barbecue",
      "to rent out",
      "to be (located)",
      "to sell"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "verstehen",
    "correct": "to understand",
    "choices": [
      "to understand",
      "to stay",
      "to drink",
      "to order"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(sich) vorstellen",
    "correct": "to introduce",
    "choices": [
      "seven",
      "to take",
      "to introduce",
      "to thank"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "warten",
    "correct": "to wait",
    "choices": [
      "to know",
      "to play",
      "to wait",
      "to taste"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(sich) waschen",
    "correct": "to wash",
    "choices": [
      "at/in the back",
      "to be allowed",
      "to wash",
      "to congratulate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "werden",
    "correct": "to become",
    "choices": [
      "to be able to",
      "to meet",
      "to become",
      "allow"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "wiederholen",
    "correct": "to repeat",
    "choices": [
      "to be able to",
      "to belong",
      "to get on (board)",
      "to repeat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "willkommen",
    "correct": "…",
    "choices": [
      "to fill out",
      "one billion",
      "…",
      "to fetch"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "wissen",
    "correct": "to know",
    "choices": [
      "to know",
      "to live",
      "to cost",
      "to (have a) barbecue"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "wohnen",
    "correct": "to live",
    "choices": [
      "to play",
      "to live",
      "together",
      "to take with"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "wollen",
    "correct": "to want",
    "choices": [
      "to tell",
      "to love",
      "would like to",
      "to want"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "zahlen",
    "correct": "to pay",
    "choices": [
      "to look",
      "to pay",
      "to need",
      "to transfer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "zufrieden",
    "correct": "happy",
    "choices": [
      "to take",
      "to mean",
      "happy",
      "to visit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "zusammen",
    "correct": "together",
    "choices": [
      "together",
      "to invite / treat",
      "to sleep",
      "to get up"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "zwischen",
    "correct": "between",
    "choices": [
      "to taste",
      "between",
      "to go",
      "to know"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "sieben",
    "correct": "seven",
    "choices": [
      "to be",
      "to be allowed",
      "seven",
      "to repair"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "eine Million, -en",
    "correct": "one million",
    "choices": [
      "one million",
      "to write",
      "to depart (by air)",
      "to rent out"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(sich) waschen",
    "correct": "to wash",
    "choices": [
      "to say / tell",
      "to end",
      "to wash",
      "to (have a) barbecue"
    ]
  }
];
